

Osman Uğur Demirer

Date of birth: 15/09/1997 | **Nationality:** Turkish | **Phone number:** (+90) 5335974056 (Mobile) | **Email address:**

osmanugurdemirer@outlook.com | **Github:** https://github.com/Ugurdmrer

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/osman-ugur-demirer/ | Address: Istanbul, Türkiye (Home)

ABOUT ME

Hello, my name is Osman Uğur Demirer.

Since I was 13, I have dreamed of improving myself in the IT sector due to my interest in computers, and in order to realize this dream, I have tried to reach information that will improve myself in my spare time, this effort and desire still continues.

Instead of my passion for IT, I studied insurance in my high school life. About 3 years ago, I decided to gain experience in the field of IT and worked for 1.5 years at a hosting company called Climax Host. In this way, I had the opportunity to develop myself in the fields of networking, software and operating systems.

I want to improve my skills more in the field of IT by relying on my youth and my determination to learn, to find new job opportunities and to experience the experiences that these will add to me.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/02/2023 - 21/06/2023 İstanbul, Türkiye

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ISTANBUL GEDIK UNIVERSITY

This is the job that i have experience with API's and RestApi's i experience the database's such as MongoDB, mysql and also i work with python and flask, i did some web scraping and i work with open source education softwares such as moodle and bigbluebutton.

11/04/2022 - CURRENT İstanbul, Türkiye

WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER SAYGWARE

This is our firm that we create on the past with my friends and we still work togather also we build websites in this firm.

08/2015 - 06/2016 Istanbul, Türkiye

INSURER KUZEN SIGORTA

The firm was an insurance agent and it was my first work experience. I did my internship as a salesman in the company.

08/2019 - 03/2021 Frankfurt, Germany

SYSTEM ADMIN CLIMAX HOST

During my time at this company, I took care of the sales, server maintenance and customer support departments of the company and it was also my first remote working experience.

Website https://climax.host/

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

12/2017 - 07/2018 Istanbul, Türkiye

LANGUAGE SCHOOL American Culture - English

Final grade C1

2010 - 2016 Istanbul, Türkiye

HIGH SCHOOL Dilek Sabancı Vocational And Technical High School - Insurance

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): TURKISH

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	B2	C1	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Programming Languages

JavaScript | CSS | Python | HTML5

Skills

Networking | Web Scraping | Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) | React.js Basics | SQL and NoSql databases | MySQL & MongoDB | Jinja2 Template | MS Office (MS Word, MS Powerpoint, MS Excel, MS) | GIT (GitHub) | Web servers (Apache, Nginx, LiteSpeed) | Ubuntu | Kali Linux (Debian)

Frameworks

BoostrapCSS, TailwindCSS | Python Flask REST API | Python FastAPI

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: A2 **Driving Licence:** B

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Video Games I've been involved with video games since I was 15 years old.

Sports I did kickboxing for 2.5 years.

I also play football and basketball on a regular basis.

Art I really love listening to music, watching movies, theatre and TV shows.